veeble.org 2014-09-01

# Privacy Policy - Veeble

### Privacy Policy

Because Veeble takes privacy issues seriously and wants to protect your rights we have established this Privacy Policy. Please make sure you understand our policy on this matter and feel free to contact us if you have any questions or issues regarding this document.

* * *

Personal Information Usage  
Veeble will not search to sell, rent, lend, exchange or give your mail address, your zip code or your phone number at a third party without your explicit permission. The information provided by you are protected and can’t be found by a outside person. Veeble will use the customer's personal information only as reasonably necessary to provide contracted services and to collect fees owed.

Disclosure of Personal Information  
The Customer authorizes Veeble to use it's name, business name, city or country informations and comments in marketing documents or as testimonials on Veeble's web site. At any time, the Customer can send a written notice to withdraw this authorization. Veeble will only disclose personal information to a third party if required by law as evidenced by a valid Court Order of competent jurisdiction or to a collection agency if needed.

Disclosure of Non-Personal Aggregates  
Veeble could share with its partners or third parties a non-personal anonymous aggregate of informations about its users or web site visitors. For example, we could provide statistics data about the number of users of a particular area. The transmitted information is for statistic and will not reveal in any way your identity.

Emails  
We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages visitors access or visit and information volunteered by the visitor, such as survey information, inquiries, and/or site registrations. We also send periodic marketing emails/newsletters.  
If you do not want to receive e-mails from us in the future, please let us know by sending an e-mail to us at the above address and telling us that you do not want to receive e-mail from our company.

Periodic Mailings  
If you supply us with your postal address online you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by sending an e-mail to the above address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we use for promotional purposes.

Voice Calls  
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding account verification or other account related information, billing or promotions that we believe may be of interest. Please provide us with your correct phone number.

Questions or Comments  
For additional questions, please contact our team using our contact form. 

* * *
